Red and Blue, ready?
Let us start!
Keerthi! Keerthi! Keerthi!
Come on, Keerthi!
Sister, come on! Nail it!
Come on, slam her!
-Hey!
-Wow!
Come on, grab her leg!
Come on, grab her! Slam her!
Yes!
Come on, slam her!
Wow!
-Congratulations!
-Thank you, sir.
Well done!
The next plan of our academy
is to conduct
the Submission Wrestling Tournament.
Players from other towns will participate.
But I expect your performance
to stand out from others. Okay?
-Sure, sir.
-Good!
-The last slam where you nailed her.
-Yes.
You applied my technique with diligence.
Uncle, there's no match for you.
You played well, dear!
Who is home?
I wonder who has arrived.
What's wrong with you?
Please wait.
I'll get her changed into a saree.
Not necessary.
We have seen enough.
The broker told us
that she quit wrestling.
Once she's married,
she won't indulge in wrestling.
Why are you making her quit wrestling?
If everyone gets married,
then who will win medals for our nation?
I'll get straight to the point.
You could get your younger daughter
married to my son.
We can fix a date
during the upcoming auspicious day.
-You may leave.
-Oh, God!
Why would you do such a thing, mom?
They said the girl would quit wrestling
after the marriage.
How could you lead a life with a wrestler?
If she slams you,
you will die on the spot!
She won't stop with you.
She'll slam me as well.
Shut up and keep walking.
Did you hear what they said?
That's why I didn't want her
to take up wrestling.
You never listened!
You're scolding me as if I'm Aamir Khan
from Dangal
and she excelled because of my training.
It's all because of you!
You took her along
to every match you played.
That's what inspired her to play.
Why do you think I took her along?
If I got hurt,
I needed someone to inform my family.
That's why I took her along.
How'd I know--
Enough!
Many suitors visited.
Nothing seems to work out.
Brother, don't worry.
It's my responsibility
to get Keerthi married.
Hopeless! You're old and single!
And you expect me to believe you.
I'm afraid she will never get married.
Just the thought of it…
Brother!
Dad!
Doctor, how is he now?
Mrs. Sarojini, your husband,
suffered a second attack.
But he is out of danger now.
Nothing to worry about.
He will be under observation
for two days.
Keep him away from stress.
I'm why everyone is sad sitting
at the hospital.
My love for wrestling is the reason.
How do I say this?
It's an eighteen-year-old story.
Keerthi was six at that time.
When I used to ask her
if she was dad or mom's pet,
she'd reply, "I'm uncle's pet."
Such was our bonding.
I used to take her to school.
-I used to feed and put her to bed.
-Bye, uncle.
She'd always be with me.
During that time,
a wrestling coach arrived.
I thought wrestling was easy
-and joined the class.
-Stop.
But my tummy did get
in the way of my desire.
Hey!
After seeing me perform in a fight,
the coach spoke to me.
You can't wrestle
if your life depended on it!
-You're not fit for wrestling.
-Oh, no!
For God's sake, please find another hobby.
Coach!
Even if the world tells you you've lost,
you don't lose until you believe so.
Still, I continued to lose.
My defeat used to upset Keerthi.
Uncle, why did you loosen your leg
when that man locked your neck?
You could've tripped him
by applying the entire weight on his leg.
Why did I not think of it?
Tell me, how do you know about it?
Keerthi hoped that I should
at least win a match.
Until the end, it remained a dream.
Bye!
Come on, raid!
I was not good at wrestling.
But Keerthi,
who grew up watching me was well-versed.
Yes!
She participated in wrestling held
at school and won.
It felt like I won.
Keerthi joined college.
I hoped she would study in college.
But she was determined
and continued to wrestle.
Wrestling is a men's sport.
It won't suit you.
Sport does not have a gender.
If you check out the playground,
everything is a sport.
What if your face gets damaged wrestling?
No one would marry you.
My brother was determined
to get Keerthi married.
Is your daughter a wrestler?
No… She used to do it in college.
-The short hair makes her look like a guy.
-Yes.
A hundred sovereigns gold,
ten lakh cash, and an Innova car.
If this is fine with you,
we'll take this further.
It's an insult to me as a woman
to get married by offering a dowry.
You may please leave.
Eve teasing got added
to the list of wrestling and dowry.
A few boys
at college harassed her sister, Raji.
She beat the hell out of them.
SREE NEELAKANTA GOVERNMENT
SAMSKRITHA COLLEGE, PATTAMBI
Hey, run!
How dare you harass women?
Oh, God!
The video of Keerthi thrashing the boys
at the bus stand
went viral on social media and WhatsApp.
Hereafter, no one from Kerala
will ask for your daughter's hand
in marriage.
If you still insist, we will check
for suitors in another state.
God help us!
It would have been a surprise
if my brother hadn't got a stroke
after all this chaos.
Dad!
What did the doctor say?
Did he say I'll die sooner?
Dad.
I'm not worried that I'm going to die.
I'll die at peace
if I see you get married.
For the women of our country,
family comes first.
Dreams and ambition come
after everything else.
Dad. Dad…
I can make it big as a wrestler.
Trust me.
We are middle-class people.
It won't suit us.
Don't forget you have a younger sister.
You must think about her life as well.
Please give up wrestling.
Why are you crying?
Is it because your father
asked you to give up wrestling?
He asked you not
to take part in a competition.
Get married and continue
to wrestle inside your house.
Confused?
Every married woman is a wrestler.
Every day, women have
to wrestle with their husbands.
Did you wrestle with Grandpa?
Of course, I did!
He got it well from me,
and now he's resting in peace.
Poor soul!
Similarly, you will find a man
who'd wrestle with you for life.
Veera! Veera!
Dude, go on a raid. Slay them all!
Don't spare anyone!
Kabaddi! Kabaddi!
-Come on!
-Come!
Kabaddi! Kabaddi!
Veera!
Kabaddi!
Yeh!
We may arrive torpidly
If we stare, it will be ablaze
When it dawns
We will create a fuss
Collars up
Coolers on
The guy is handsome
The girl is beautiful
We are playful at sight
But our grit is might
Take a new route
Dance, thagida thagida thagida
This town is our fort
That bears my mighty picture
I worked my charm
You fell for it
Veera!
Has arrived!
How is she?
Please, turn around.
In a street of coconut trees
We are the toddy shops
We are the men
Who swim around pretty trouts
-Hey, wearing garland
-We sear like crackers
-If we come with trust
-We will take care of you
Hey guys, deal the cards
Let's play during the day
Where are we going to study?
We are always after fun
And create problems
Beautiful like a bud
About the right size
A new bindi on the forehead
She is a yellow angel
We may arrive torpidly
If we stare, it will be ablaze
When it dawns
We will create a fuss
Collars up
Coolers on
The guy is handsome
The girl is beautiful
What about her?
Wait. How far did she pursue her studies?
She just graduated from ITI.
Such an educated girl won't suit me.
I said ITI, not IIT.
Even that is too much for me.
I hope I'm making sense, Sattam.
We are playful at sight
But our grit is might
Take a new route
Dance, thagida thagida thagida
This town is our fort
That bears my mighty picture
I worked my charm
You fell for it
Please turn around.
You don't have to say anything.
Hereafter don't take me
to find you a match.
To hell with your preconditions.
Hey, what's wrong with his preconditions?
It's not wrong that he expects
his wife to be less educated than him.
He pursued it only till eighth grade.
That, too, he failed.
In this age, it's hard
to find someone so less educated.
Thanks to COVID-19,
everyone passed out of high school.
We should look for a match ourselves.
How do you think I found my wife?
Brother, how far is she educated?
She pursued it till fourth grade.
-How about you?
-Seventh grade!
Listen, the Midday Meal Scheme
was introduced to lure people like you.
Still, you didn't go to school.
Back in the day, passing seventh grade
is considered as passing out MBBS today.
Give me a scalpel. I'll perform surgery.
Nothing would go wrong
if he married an educated girl.
Sattam, an educated girl,
will ask a hundred questions.
But an uneducated girl will listen
to what I say.
An educated girl will talk about
current affairs.
An uneducated girl won't know
what's happening around her.
An educated girl will speak about
socialism, communism, and Periyarism.
But an uneducated girl will stick
to making curry and rasam for me.
To sum up, an uneducated girl
will abide by me.
Whereas I should
abide by an educated girl.
It's not just that.
If the wife is less educated than you,
we can speak English as we please.
Watch me now.
Hey, come here!
One plate of fish fry.
Come on, hurry up!
How was it?
Brother, what you spoke is not English.
It's Hindi!
Whether it is Hindi or English,
she is oblivious to it.
I'm good as long as I get a fish fry.
Okay, I can make peace with him
nit-picking about her studies.
Why is he rejecting girls
because they have short hair?
Listen, long hair is a beautiful asset
for women.
With short hair, she's nothing but a man.
Do you know what kind
of hair a girl should have?
Long hair should run to her back
and hang above the ankles.
When she walks,
it should oscillate like a pendulum.
-What?
-I meant her hair.
You see, the hair that flows in the air
should gracefully brush my face.
When she lies next to me,
I want to embrace her hair.
The fragrance of it…
A thick skull like you won't get it.
There's another advantage to long hair.
If your wife speaks against you,
you can swirl, hold, stamp, and beat her.
She can neither run nor hide.
Uncle, find me an obedient girl
like auntie.
Then you'd have to marry your aunt.
For kids from the 2000s,
it's enough if it's a girl.
But you have remained single
with all your stupid preconditions.
Bloody 90s kids!
Hey, are you going to puke?
-My wife is calling.
-Why is he scared of her?
Uncle, he's such a weakling.
THE LAW WILL DO ITS DUTY
-Son!
-Yeah!
I thought he was carrying law books
inside the backpack.
But he's carrying a mini-saloon.
-Hopeless man!
-I'm taking my leave.
It's better not to drink
than humiliate yourself.
You'd realize when you get married.
I'd remain the same even after marriage.
Wanna bet?
I don't want to bet. Repeat what you said.
I'd remain the same even after marriage.
That's more like it!
This is enough.
-It'll be helpful in the future.
-Get lost!
Get going!
There's a council meeting in the morning.
Be present without fail.
Folks, how long should we wait?
Is Das coming or not?
Someone, please find out.
I thought of building a factory, offering
employment, and developing the village.
But you're against it like anti-Indians.
What is your problem?
We're not against the idea of development.
But if the development is going to pollute
the water, what do you expect?
The dye waste from your factory--
Old man, dye waste is obvious.
What else do you expect?
Hey, stop joking!
Wise men are talking.
I'll thrash you to dust.
-Hey!
-To hell with you!
Hey, Sattam!
Das, I hope you're aware four cows died
after drinking the water from the pond.
Perhaps the cows died of disease.
Why are you blaming it on me?
More than half the village folks
drink water from that pond.
Everyone seems healthy.
How do you know?
Go and check at the hospital.
Every day many children get admitted
to the hospital.
It's not like they are all dead.
Sattam! He seems irrational.
-Let's shut down his factory.
-Sure!
Look, you're the President
of this village, not India.
Das, curb your arrogance.
Sattam, file a case.
We'll take him to court.
To prove the charges against the accused,
the petitioner is granted one more month
to gather evidence.
The court informed
that until then,
there would be no stay put on the factory.
Sattam, gather evidence
and build a strong case.
Das is clever.
He would change the course of the case.
-We will be humiliated in court.
-I'll handle it.
Son. we're going to buy booze
and then drive to the farm.
Uncle,
today is mother's death anniversary.
-So?
-You know that I don't drink on this day.
I used to take money
from your mother to drink.
You didn't just take money
from his mother.
You took money from his stepmother too.
-You mean our stepmother?
-Yes!
Hey!
Hey! Watch out!
Had you bumped me,
what would've happened?
I don't even have insurance.
Step out of the car. I said step out!
It's the car that would get damaged
by bumping into you.
Hello, Mr. Big fat paunch!
Hey, Ratnam!
-Wait, I'm coming.
-Come on!
-Hey, how are you?
-I'm good!
What are you doing over here?
I came to see my friend George.
He's an advocate over here.
Oh, is it? This is my friend, Ganeshan.
We studied together till seventh grade.
Your uncle studied
only till seventh grade.
Showing off!
-Hop inside the car.
-Where to?
-I need to talk to you.
-I have other work, dude.
Ganesha, you used to look handsome
like Aravind Swami.
What happened to you?
What to do? I have been busy.
Come on.
You used to be handsome like Abbas.
-But now you have changed.
-Did you hear that?
I believe these two have never seen
good-looking men in their lives.
What are you whispering?
Nothing, Mr. Handsome hunk,
you carry on.
Ratnam, you have a lavish life.
-Come on, it all belongs to my nephew.
-Oh, is it!
Ratnam, is your nephew not drinking?
-He does not drink.
-Nephew!
-Why don't you have a drink?
-No thanks. You carry on.
-What about a small one?
-No thanks.
Don't force him.
Such a great character,
and that too in 2022.
Is your nephew married?
Not in this life!
Are his stars maligned?
Not just one
but all his stars are maligned.
I don't get it!
I said ITI, not IIT.
I thinking
of getting Keerthi married to him.
But their preconditions are hard to meet.
Ganesha, seeing you think,
I believe you have a match for my nephew.
He figured it out!
Yes, there's a girl.
-But she is not from here.
-Where's she from?
Palakkad!
-Palakkad, uh!
-Palakkad won't work out.
It's not like
it's near the Pakistan border.
It's near the Kerala border.
-It's an hour's drive.
-Yeah!
-Just 50 kilometers, nephew!
-Yes.
Who is the girl? And how far
has she pursued her education?
She is my niece.
She studied till seventh grade.
-Only till seventh grade?
-Yes.
Why not more?
It's because you said
your nephew studied till eighth grade.
That's why I stopped after seventh grade.
Ganesha, how long is your niece's hair?
I said Kerala, and you're still in doubt.
In India, only Kerala women
have the longest hair.
Their long hair will dance to their tunes.
It has to be trimmed every month.
Why do you have to trim it every month?
If they don't trim it,
they will trip on it.
Idiot, it'll get tangled.
Ganesha, you better crash here tonight.
Tomorrow we'll go together
and see the girl.
-Oh, God, no!
-What happened?
You see, if you're coming to see my niece,
I need to make the necessary arrangements.
If you show up unexpectedly,
my brother will get a stroke.
Then there will be no wedding.
Does your brother often get a stroke?
Ratna, you wouldn't understand.
I have too much to do. I'm leaving!
You bring your nephew to Palakkad.
We'll sort it out!
I can't, and I won't!
I can't wear this.
Stop overreacting!
It's not like women don't use it at all.
I can't marry someone
who comes with terms and conditions.
Every man has an expectation
of the woman, he's about to marry.
Women, too, expect men to be
well-settled in life before marriage.
Mom, don't speak for the sake of it.
Don't you think he'll find out
if it's fake after marriage?
It'll be humiliating!
Dear, we can spew a thousand lies
to make a marriage.
We are only going to lie about two things.
Your education and your hair.
Uncle!
It's wrong to say
a high school pass-out is a graduate.
You're a BSc graduate, but we will lie
and say you're a seventh-grade pass-out.
This is not a lie
because you did pass seventh grade.
You won't find innocent guys
anywhere else but Tamil Nadu.
Once you're married,
everything will fall into place.
She's right, dear!
Please consider your father's condition.
Sister, please say okay to it.
Do as you please!
My dear…
-Success!
How did I forget about this?
If they look at these pictures,
we're doomed!
Here you go!
Phew! Welcome son!
-Welcome, everyone.
-Ganesha, I hope everything is ready.
Perfectly ready!
My brother won't get a stroke.
-Greetings!
-Welcome!
-All good?
-We are well!
Sarojini!
Son, be careful. You might spill.
Dear, you look lovely with long hair.
What?
The old lady speaks
as if she's seeing her for the first time.
You're right.
She recently got out of eye surgery.
So, everything seems new to her.
Mom, please stay silent for a while.
I remember your daughter from somewhere…
But I don't seem to place her.
Have you ever been to Palakkad before?
I did not!
Neither my daughter has visited Pollachi.
Obviously, you did not meet her.
I did not mean to say I met her in person.
-But I feel I knew her--
-Hey, shut up!
-What is your name?
-Keerthi.
How far are you educated?
Seventh grade, right?
Why do you ask him?
It's you who studied.
Agreed that she pursued education,
-but it's he, who took her to the school.
-Yes, Ratnam.
Oh!
She is very absent-minded.
That's why we stopped her education
after seventh grade.
Oh, okay!
-Am I right?
-Yeah! Yeah!
Hey! Hey!
Stop staring at her.
Only if you say something
can we take it forward.
Sattam, how can I not like her?
-Look at her hair. They're dark and long.
-True that.
No girl in our town
has long hair like her.
I didn't expect it to be so long.
But it's longer than I expected.
Kerala women are the best.
I love Kerala. I love Pinarayi Vijayan.
I concur the boy likes the girl.
Let's finalize everything else.
I did not save much.
Whatever I have, I will equally
distribute it between my daughters.
It'll be great
if you could give us an idea.
He's the only son. He owns a house
and 20 acres of coconut grove.
There's no scarcity of income.
Moreover, your daughter
won't have the trouble of in-laws.
Ratnam, your demands are right.
But let us say it out in the open.
Forty sovereigns of gold
and four lakh cash.
On top of it, we'll offer everything
required for the dowry.
Okay?
Forty sovereigns of gold
and four lakh cash?
-Get up, uncle.
-Hear me out!
We don't need this alliance.
-Son, I didn't mean to offend you.
-Come on, let's go!
Please sit down.
We'll negotiate better terms.
This is not a business transaction
to negotiate.
Look at your daughter. She's so modest.
You have raised a lovely
and modest daughter.
That too during these times.
Rightfully I should offer a dowry
to marry your daughter.
Tell me! How much should I offer?
-Hey! Hey!
-Come on, tell me!
Son, you may say no now.
I hope you won't trouble us
after the marriage.
Mother, how could you doubt me?
It's an insult to me as a man
to take dowry.
Oh, beloved, casting your net
In the Kerala riverbank
Oh, beloved
Having eyes like a sickle
Oh, she's sharp-witted
She is the smart one from Kuyilimala
Oh, beloved, casting your net
In the Kerala riverbank
Do you have a bundle of sweetness?
Do you have divinity?
Stepping on the grinding stone
You walk
You shine like the Sun
I wish to hug you
By blinking your eyes
You enchant me
Are you the guardian
Of his life henceforth?
Is your saree pallu
For hiding your coyness? Beat it!
Keeping betel leaves on the plate
Playing music, she will walk
So delicately like a bud
Smearing the holy vermilion
On the forehead
Hearts come together
She will laugh like
A statue made of silk
Do you have a bundle of sweetness?
Do you have divinity?
Your blush is like a musical note
Your smile is like a painting
The moon is searching for you
To take your color on to it
Beautiful long hair
Wearing the mighty crown
I dream of holding your hands every day
Your blinking eyes
Hold a small story
The sound of your bangles
Mesmerize me
The little finger you hold
You go around me
You feel like a companion
Completely lose yourself
Are you the guardian
Of his life henceforth?
Is your saree pallu
For hiding your coyness?
Keeping betel leaves on the plate
Playing music, she will walk
So delicately like a bud
Smearing the holy vermilion
On the forehead
Hearts come together
She will laugh like
A statue made of silk
Do you have a bundle of sweetness?
Do you have divinity?
Oh, beloved, casting your net
In the Kerala riverbank
Do you have divinity?
Oh, beloved
Having eyes like a sickle
Do you have divinity?
-What is it, uncle?
-Eh!
We're not Northerners to dance
at our weddings.
We're true, Tamizhans.
We're the people who riot at weddings.
I noticed you smiling at your wife.
-Is it wrong?
-Yes!
We can smile at anyone in the world.
But we should never smile at our wives.
Because they will take advantage of it.
Uncle, you see,
she's the perfect wife I dreamt of.
That's why I slipped a bit on seeing her.
This is the weakness of all men.
Son, bear this in mind.
They say it's the first night.
It applies only to women.
Because their life begins on that night.
But for men, it's last night.
Because after that night,
their life is doomed.
-Doomed?
-Don't ask for an explanation.
Show me your hand.
-What is this thread?
-This is not an ordinary thread.
This thread keeps the wife in control.
I ordered it from a shaman online.
Go and get your wife under control.
What is this uncle?
It's a thread blessed by our deity.
I'm tying this to your wrist
to keep your anger under control.
It is not required, uncle.
It's a matter of faith. Don't refuse it.
-Come on, it's just a thread.
-Listen to your grandma!
-You better.
-Why so many hairpins?
You see, during the first night,
the grooms are very aggressive!
Four hairpins won't be enough.
Your extensions will fall apart.
-Add ten-fifteen pins.
-Once you get inside, fall on his feet.
-Why?
-It's a tradition, dear.
Don't ask unnecessary questions.
-Could you please stand up?
-Why?
I need to touch your feet…
Oh!
Be well!
How come you have strong arms?
It's bone weight.
Oh, do you do a lot of chores?
Very good. Sit down.
How do I begin?
Let me tell you everything about myself.
I may look like a fun person.
But in reality, I'm very serious.
I'm short-tempered,
and I may raise my hand.
To me, respect is paramount.
No matter what the situation is,
you must treat me with respect.
Please don't give me cheesy nicknames
like youngsters do these days.
It will not sit well
with me. Understand?
Why are you blinking?
Do you understand?
Come on!
Listen, I need to tell you about myself.
You can tell me in the morning.
No, I have to say it right now.
Oh, God! She does not understand my needs.
Do you have another love
that I don't know of?
Do you want me to help you elope
with your lover?
-No, you got me wrong.
-Then, what is it?
-My hair…
-Your hair is great!
You see, that's the problem!
That's not a problem at all.
We're getting late.
-One minute!
-Who the hell is it?
UNCLE CALLING
Uncle!
The idiot does not know when to call.
Go ahead and speak.
Listen, you're not at an exam.
It's your wedding night.
If you answer the question correctly,
the result will be negative.
What are you saying, uncle?
On the wedding night,
women usually open up,
thinking their husband is being honest.
You, please don't make that mistake.
-Uncle, please hear me out--
-Listen!
Stop interrupting and listen to me!
After a long time,
your father is sleeping peacefully.
Please don't do anything
that'll put him to sleep forever.
Phew!
You were about to say something
about your hair.
I heard that you love long hair.
-You heard it right.
-My uncle told me.
So, would you like me
to use regular or organic shampoo?
You're smart.
This natural and fragrant hair,
demands organic shampoo.
Come on!
I'm dead!
Oh, no!
Oh God, no!
Stop!
What is this?
-Hair.
-I know it's hair.
Why did you not take a head bath?
I did take a head bath.
No one can cheat me.
Go! Go and take a head bath.
We just consummated our marriage.
And she's unaware
she must take a head bath.
Now, this is considered a head bath.
Hereafter, continue to do so.
Go.
I'm smarter!
Veera!
A lot of people have come to meet you.
They're all my folks!
They must be heading to a council meeting.
They don't go without me.
-Greetings, son.
-Greetings, brother!
-So, uncle, where are we going today?
-Same old Puliyankolai.
-It doesn't seem to end.
-We'll end it today!
Okay, get inside. Start the car!
This thread keeps the wife in control.
I ordered it from a shaman online.
Keerthi!
What is it?
When the husband is leaving,
the wife has to smile and bid him goodbye.
That's a good trait of a wife.
Come! Come over here!
Move to your left.
Move to your right.
Bring your hair in the front.
Give me a little smile.
Now you can bid me goodbye.
Let's go!
Hey, Pazhani, come over here.
Tell me, brother!
Take this chain to the pawnbroker
and get 50, 000 rupees.
Then head straight to my house
and say, I borrowed 50, 000 rupees
to pay the school fees for my children.
Please give this to him.
And hand it over to my wife.
Then sing praises. No one is as noble
as our brother in the village.
He's a philanthropist.
After that, you can leave.
Okay brother.
Hey, Sadalai, come over here.
You follow Pazhani.
Ten minutes after Pazhani leaves my house,
go there and ask for me.
And say, my wife is in labor
and it's an emergency.
Plead and ask, I need 50, 000 rupees.
She will call me.
I'll ask her to check if there's money.
To which she would say,
Just now, Pazhani returned 50, 000 rupees
he borrowed from you.
I'll ask her to give you that money.
You take that money and
head to the pawnbroker
and take back my pawned chain.
-Get going!
-Okay, brother.
You could have instead not gone through
so much trouble.
If I don't do this,
there will be no respect for me.
What are you getting at?
First three months after marriage
is a crucial period for husbands.
The impression we make on our wives
will stay for life.
She will think, my husband
is an important man in this village.
Everyone looks up to him as a God.
It's enough that I make her believe I'm
the one to whom everyone comes for help.
For life, she won't talk back to me.
I'm sure your wife will be impressed!
Not enough!
We need to keep throwing a yorker
to keep them in line.
Hello!
-Is sir home?
-Who are you?
MLA wanted to speak to him.
He's not home.
Shall I give you his mobile number?
No, no! MLA will speak
to him only over the landline number.
On the tenth,
there's a textile showroom inauguration.
Sir, has to cut the ribbon!
Sure, I'll let him know.
I know, sir is very busy.
-Please make a note of the date.
-Okay.
-Hello?
-Hello, I'm the Bank Manager.
Mr. Rahul, speaking!
I want to speak to Mr. Veera.
Where is your husband?
Hi, I'm Keerthi, his wife.
He's not at home at this moment.
I think he should return
in the next thirty minutes.
But may I know what this is in regards to?
-And which bank is it?
-Okay, finishing!
Hello?
I thought you said your wife
pursued education till seventh grade.
Yes. Why do you ask?
She didn't understand the English I spoke.
It's enough.
Your wife might get scared.
Huh. Just one more incident.
I want to sweep her off her feet.
Mani, a group, is loitering, holding
these fliers, and asking for donations.
Ask them to come home in the morning.
Bye, Sattam.
Hey, this is too much!
-Madam!
Hey! We're not beggars!
We're here
to request a donation for the temple.
And you guys are yearning like beggars.
That is why people end up donating
chump change.
Shut up and watch!
Madam!
-Who is it?
-Is, sir, home?
He's in the shower. How can I help?
This Friday, we're organizing a carnival
at Uthukuli Deity temple.
Please speak to your husband
and help us with a donation.
Here you go.
Please show this to your husband.
GRACIOUS DEITY AMMAN'S TEMPLE CARNIVAL
Listen, people have come
asking for a donation.
There is one lakh inside the desk drawer.
Give it to them.
-One lakh?
-Yes!
Why would you donate such a large sum?
Donations should be given
with an open heart.
Do as I say!
Here you go!
Instead of money,
you're bringing me an old newspaper.
There is one lakh rupee inside it.
One lakh?
She is not kidding.
It is one lakh rupees.
Who is this philanthropist?
My husband!
Make sure you bring this great person
to the carnival.
Hereafter, we will honor him
with all the titles.
-Bye-bye. Goodbye, let's go!
-Thank you, madam!
The judge is very strict.
If they gather evidence against us,
it'll become tough to save the factory.
I suggest you settle this matter
out of court.
Don't you know how to cook?
How could you not take away
the stones from the rice?
Don't get worked up!
Earlier, Veera was single.
Now he is married.
Why don't we kidnap his wife?
Where is she from?
I'm leaving.
-Why is your hair all wet?
-I just took a bath.
-I need to dry them.
-When? After you catch a cold?
Come! Don't overthink, come!
I have noticed that you never
hair dry using benzoin.
Didn't your mother teach you anything?
It's not enough that you grow your hair.
You have to maintain it.
That's quintessential.
If not, you'll start losing hair.
-Hurry up, brother.
-Hold your horses. I'll be there.
You draw a good rangoli.
Hey, throw on the offside.
Come on, throw to this side.
Is this how you play?
You spoiled my rangoli.
Why did you draw a rangoli out here?
Where else do you want me to
draw a rangoli?
Go and play at your house.
-Ball?
-I won't return your ball.
Get lost! I said, get lost!
Fooling around early in the morning.
Hello!
I'm bringing friends over for lunch.
Hunt a rooster and make curry.
I don't know how to make chicken curry.
Hello?
Hey, stop!
I said, stop!
Even if you climb up,
I won't spare you.
Hey, don't run!
Hey, I got you!
Are you trying to hunt a rooster?
If we help you hunt,
would you return the ball?
-Hey, catch it.
-Don't let it go. Grab it!
Guys, come around and catch it!
-Come on, hurry up!
-Don't lose it!
-Hurry up!
-Where the hell is it going?
-Come on! Come on!
-It's on the tree.
Shake the tree.
-I will catch it.
-I will catch it!
-I caught you!
-You're getting cooked today!
-What now?
-Now put tomatoes.
-Did you add them?
-Yes, I added tomatoes.
What else?
I added coriander,
curry leaves, green chilies,
and finally, I added tomatoes too.
-Is that enough?
-Now mix it and cook well.
Okay, I'll take it from here.
Sister, are you having guests over?
No!
Then why are you making so much food?
My husband is bringing over
his friends for lunch.
Are you cooking for
your husband's friends?
Yes!
We wouldn't have helped you hunt
if we had known about it earlier.
Let's go!
What happened?
-It's because we don't get along well.
Listen, you should not disrespect elders.
Elders? They are all cheapskates.
Are you guys serious?
They will head out to the council
to resolve an issue.
But they will blow the issue
out of proportion.
Most of the time,
the council meetings end in a fight.
There are instances they got beaten up.
Even now, they're playing kabaddi
at the school playground.
And you're here cooking
for those cheapskates.
He asked you to cook
and didn't turn up for lunch.
And you believed he'd come
and starve yourself.
If we keep up the charade to eat
only after the husband eats,
then for life, we'll be hungry.
Husbands will find their meals
as they please.
Your husband might be wealthy.
But how long could he mooch off it?
He has emptied most of his wealth.
Now only this house and the farm are left.
It's up to you to save whatever is left.
-So--
-Veera grew up without his parents.
His uncle is not a good guardian
and did not raise him well.
At least you stay patient with him
and get him on track.
For thirty years, they spoil their sons
and get them married to us.
And the mothers-in-law expect us
to straighten them out.
It's not our job to get them on track.
It's not like we were born to do it.
I wonder what mothers do
with their sons for thirty years.
He always hangs out with useless friends.
No one is capable of anything.
They drink to their necks.
You say that no one has a job.
-How do they get money to drink?
-Don't even ask!
Even if they don't have money,
they'll borrow to drink.
Brother,
why do you not like your better half?
Who said so?
Every man likes a better half very much.
But it has
to be another man's better half.
In this world full of shapes,
these men are with no form.
That's an apt description of these men.
If we start taking a form
the world can't take it.
We live a life bound by truth.
Men talk too much of themselves.
Do you think they can bear the labor pain?
They experience pain
only when they're in labor.
But we men struggle our entire lives
to raise the child.
-It's unimaginable…
-To heck with them!
Try bathing and changing diapers.
Can they do it?
Back then, my grandma
had ten children, raised them,
and handled all the chores.
At present, it's just one child,
and they expect us to help them.
Nowadays, there's a machine available
for every job.
Switching on machines is simple.
That is why I suggest,
whether we men have a job or not,
leave the house in the morning.
Once you leave in the morning,
return only at night
after the soap operas.
That's the beauty of manhood!
They get well-dressed in the morning
and leave.
But they're unaware of
where they're headed.
We're the head of the family for namesake.
But we don't even get space
in the cupboard to keep our clothes.
Women buy sarees for every occasion
and pile them in the cupboard.
But they'd dress up
as if they have no clothes
and wear torn nighties all the time.
Damn!
Except for weddings, they wear nighties
to every place they visit.
They look like a
cylinder wrapped in cloth.
That's such a turn-off!
When we come home at night,
if they receive us well-dressed in saree
and flowers,
we will get enticed.
-Rightly said!
-No wonder our ancestors had many kids.
Sarees are the leading cause.
The saree is the sexiest attire
in the world.
But the women don't wear them.
Why can't they wear a saree?
As if we wear a saree,
they'd ravish us.
Only I know the struggle
I went through to have a child.
For these men,
the nighties are more than enough.
You should glare at your wife
for no reason.
If they mildly glare at us,
we should sternly glare at them.
Call them out and give them a tight slap,
even if you don't find a reason.
If they land one slap,
we should return it with two tight slaps.
You see, we can't straighten our wives
with love.
Only violence works.
Husbands can't be straightened
with sentiments.
We need to whack the hell out of them!
Come on, ladies, let's go.
Your husband's uncle is the root cause
of all your problems.
Make sure your husband does not
hang out with him.
-Nephew!
-Yeah!
-Give me your phone.
-Why?
Let us call your wife.
-Here, talk to her.
-What do I say?
Ask her to reheat the chicken curry
and make fluffy rice cakes.
They will be ready
and hot to serve by the time you reach.
-She did not pick up.
-The rice cakes?
-She did not take my call.
-Hey, stop! Stop, I say!
-Stop!
-Why did you ask me to stop?
I told you a million times
not to be romantic with your wife.
And handle her sternly.
You never listened.
I'm strict with her!
If you were strict,
she would've taken your call.
You call her again.
A wife should pick up at the first ring
when the husband calls.
She let it ring all the way.
That means she does not respect you.
Uncle, you misunderstood her.
I'm telling the truth.
Get home right now
and get your wife under control.
If not, it will ruin your life,
just like butcher Murugesan.
-Give it to me.
-Hey, you forgot about me!
Hey, I did not get on the bike.
Keerthi!
Open the door!
I ought to!
Why did you come through
the back entrance?
I wouldn't have come through
the back entrance
had you answered the door.
Oh, it was late, and I dozed off.
Let me serve you food.
Uncle was right about her.
I have to handle her differently.
Please come and eat.
-What is this?
-Food!
It's not fresh food but leftovers.
Have you heard someone eating leftovers
after being drunk?
Are you drunk?
When the husband is late,
it means he'll come home drunk.
The wife should not question him.
Oh, then, who else do you expect
to question you?
It's not the husband's duty
to answer the wife.
How do you expect me to do my job
If I keep answering you all day?
What other job do you have?
What other job?
Do you even know what a husband does?
In a day, he meets many people,
manages people,
and gets into a lot of fights.
Every day is like a war for men.
Rightfully, when the husband returns
from the war,
the wife has to pray and honor him.
Does this apply to the husbands
who loiter the entire day too?
Loitering?
I am well aware of you and your gang.
Everything, as in?
Everything, as in everything.
How?
I got to know.
Oh!
Oh, so you have assigned a pie.
Pie?
To hire someone to check
on your husband's activities.
Oh, you meant spy!
Listen, whatever you heard about me
is what I am.
It's better you come to terms with
and be a homemaker.
Instead, if you dare question me
unnecessarily…
Don't you glare!
Many beat up their wives for no reason.
But I'm particular that I will beat
only with a reason.
Don't make me do it!
Don't mess with me!
What was the case?
To excavate the pond
the Government allotted fifteen lakhs.
-Okay!
-There's a complaint
against you to have misused the money.
Hey, the fund is yet to be sanctioned.
And you come here saying
I misused the money. Are you serious?
The clerk said it got sanctioned
last month, and you signed.
He has stated the same.
Uncle, what is the problem?
Someone is conspiring against us.
Who is it?
When you stand up for the people,
they stop the honest men
and let go of the dishonest ones.
You speak to Sattam
and arrange for my bail.
Let's go!
She's really raring to go now…
How well are they gonna…
Where is your husband?
He's not home.
Why is he not home
when his newlywed wife sits at home?
She may look slim.
Still, she seems voluptuous.
Are there no men in Kerala to marry?
Why did you get married to him?
Oh, so she's from Kerala!
I watched Malena five times.
It's still fresh in my mind.
Have you watched it?
I'm sure she's seen it.
Listen.
I spent millions on this factory.
Your husband and the President
have filed a case to shut it down.
Why do they have to interfere
in my matters?
I got the President arrested
so that he does not attend the hearing.
Now I have to take care of your husband.
Make sure he does not come to court.
If he still makes it to the court,
then you'll have to find another husband.
I have many options for you.
Don't worry about it.
-What do you guys say?
-We are here!
See, they're eager!
How did it break?
I asked how did it break?
The factory owner came with his men
and threatened me.
Oh, Das came?
-What did he say?
-He asked you not to come to the court.
If I go, what would he do?
He can't do anything to me.
Here, he can only break this remote.
When the man of the house isn't home,
he shows his prowess to the women.
Once the court gives its verdict…
I'll handle him!
Listen, you don't have
to be afraid of him.
It's very common here.
You may have been a scared Malayali girl.
But now you should be
a courageous Thamizh girl.
Understood?
Do you understand?
Understood!
In this case,
based on the evidence presented
by the petitioner,
it's confirmed that the industrial wastage
from the factory
gets mixed with lake water
and has affected people's health.
Therefore, this court orders
the Kovai Collector
to shut down the factory immediately.
TRUTH ALONE TRIUMPHS
Awesome!
That's great!
Welcome, Mr. Philanthropist!
Please come, we're waiting.
-Are you from the event committee?
-Yes! Why do you ask?
To show off to my wife,
I donated a large sum.
At least return half of the amount.
Hey, I'm running short on funds.
Please return it.
Hey, speak like a philanthropist.
Look, I spent a lot.
They will give you sweets after prayers.
Be happy with what you get.
Put on the garland. Start the music.
Hello!
Hello, who is this?
One minute. Hold this. I'll be back.
Hello? Hold on!
Hello? Hello? I can't hear anything.
Yeah, speak now,
Senthil? There's no one by that name.
Is building a factory an easy task?
Do you know it's a huge process?
You filed a petty case and shut it down.
Bear this in mind.
I can splurge money and reinstate
my factory tomorrow.
But I won't do it!
Only if I kill you in front of everyone
no one will dare mess with me again.
Hey!
Give it to me!
How dare you lay your hands on our boss?
I ought to--
She's valorous!
Hey, you brought your wife to fight.
I did not ask her to fight.
She's doing it on her own.
It's all the same!
Usually, they bring along henchmen.
But you have your wife as your henchman.
Moron!
Oh, God!
-Let go!
-Does it hurt?
Hey, what are you waiting for?
Start the music!
Hey, what did you comment on that day?
I said you look voluptuous!
-How do you find my punch?
-It's hard-hitting!
Oh, God!
Hey, don't do it!
How many times did you watch Malena?
Five times!
One, two, three, four, five!
You managed to save your husband today.
But one day, we will kill him!
Hey, you have to deal with me first
to get to my husband.
I dare you!
She's valorous!
Come on, let's go.
Hop on.
She's valorous!
Hey, change the channel.
HEADLINES
The weather today…
Son, you're married to a Wonder Woman!
Hereafter, no one would
dare mess with you.
Cheers!
Where are you leaving?
I desired to wed a girl
with the town's longest hair.
The bitter truth is
that my wife has the shortest hair.
She deceived me.
She humiliated me in front of the village.
-I ought to…
-Hold on! Sit down.
-Why?
-Sit. I'll explain.
You can go home after watching this.
For your safety.
Who is this boy?
I think you're too high.
Watch closely. That's your wife.
-Keerthi?
-Yes!
Your wife is a wrestler.
What is a wrestler?
She's a kusthi champion.
-Kusthi?
-Watch this video.
Hey, hey!
Not only that,
your wife is a BSc graduate.
Does BSc mean she's more educated
than me?
A bit more educated than you.
I kept saying that I remembered
your wife from somewhere.
Yes!
I remember her from this video.
I even liked and commented on the video.
The guy who married her is doomed.
But never did I think
that you'll be her husband.
I'm very sorry!
The men your wife beat up
have been admitted to the hospital.
Doctors are stunned and mentioned
that only a person outraged and drenched
in violence can beat up like this.
Only four men can walk.
The ones you fought.
A brave woman who saved
her husband from the rowdies.
This exciting incident took place
in Pollachi.
During the temple carnival in Pollachi…
All they need is one piece of news.
They'll play it on a loop
to humiliate the person.
What are you doing over here?
Where else do you expect me to go?
When you get whacked!
I'll end up here.
Does your wife beat you?
All the wives tend to beat up
their husbands.
But that's domestic beating.
But his wife is dangerous!
Listen, they have started
the Husbands Protection Committee.
I have become a member.
If you join now
with the publicity you have attracted,
they will make you
the ambassador of the committee.
-Our protection is important.
-Yes! Yes!
Hey, I'm not scared of my wife,
unlike you.
Of course!
I'm pissed off.
It's better you go now.
Hey, hey, hey!
-My wife is calling!
-Answer the call.
-How do I speak?
-Like this!
-Bloody!
-Hello!
-Hello,
-Where are you? Are you busy?
I'm not busy. I'm nearby.
I was speaking to my friends.
-When will you be home?
-I'll be there in ten minutes.
I'll hang up.
Bye. Bye!
Okay, dear.
First thing in the morning,
join the committee.
Annoying man!
Hey, where's your bag?
Why do you need my bag?
-Give me your bag!
-What are you doing?
THE LAW WILL DO ITS DUTY
Hey, that's my toothbrush.
I don't mind!
-Okay, bye.
-Wait one minute.
Watch this before you leave.
Only then I'll be thrilled.
I'd remain the same
even after my marriage.
Keerthi, dear.
Come in.
My body is aching from the fight.
So, I could not cook today.
Please adjust tonight.
Come on. Even doctors recommend
leftover rice as the best body coolant.
I am okay with having this
for all my meals.
I…
I need to tell you one more thing.
Tell me!
I have short hair.
It's wrong of me to have hidden the truth.
-Do you know something?
-What?
Indira Gandhi had shorter hair.
Did she not become the Prime Minister?
Short hair looks good on you.
Also, I'm a BSc graduate.
That's great!
We don't have to put our kids
in coaching classes.
You can teach them.
Please pursue higher education.
I'll help you with it.
Because educating a girl
is educating a family.
-I also know…
-Wrestling, right?
The entire town saw your prowess!
You're great at it!
In these times,
self-defense for women is vital.
Please pour some water.
Is she expecting me
to make the first move?
Would I get beaten if I made a move?
I'm confused!
What is it, uncle?
Son, this Puliyankolai council
is never-ending.
They have been dragging it out!
-Fine, I'll join you.
-Join us for what?
To the council.
You're well aware
that they're not afraid of anyone.
You tried many times to reason with them.
They don't seem to budge.
So?
So, we thought of taking your wife
along with us.
Also, we all believe
the verdict will be in our favor.
-My wife?
-Yes!
Sister, come on, let's go.
Oh, no! I'm not coming!
-Take him with you.
-You don't get it do you?
As it is, they never feared Veera.
Now, he's done for good!
Come on, dear, let's go!
Taking him along is the right thing to do.
I left the stove on. I have to cook.
Our partner Veera can beat up
the entire town.
Cooking food is child's play for him.
Partner, today you're the cook!
We'll get to taste your cooking
after the council meeting.
Listen, I put out clothes to wash.
-I need to wash them.
-Brother is good at wringing people.
Washing clothes is easy for him.
Brother, wash the clothes,
put them to dry, and fold them.
It may rain today.
You see, I have to…
I was right.
To him, people are paramount.
He won't mind.
Come on! Please get inside the car.
Why are you carrying it?
Hold this for her.
Let's go. We're running late.
It is your wife's first time going to
the council meeting.
Why aren't you bidding her goodbye?
Come on, do it, son!
After all, it's just goodbye!
-Greetings, madam!
To bell the cat
She has come as a tiger
Like sugarcane to an elephant
One guy has gotten caught
If you enslave a girl
Not gonna happen
The boy shuddered
Enough!
The girl showed her strength
That's awesome!
The boy shivered
She is valorous
And can fight one-on-one
She took a wooden block
And swirled
She's valorous
Wearing gloves
Showing her arms' strength
She is going to win
You chauvinist cutie
Hit back the person
Who came to suppress you
Shave off his curled mustache
Please name my child.
-What are you doing?
-Naming your child.
You named my four other children.
And they're loitering hopeless!
You, please give the child
to your wife.
-They want you to name the child.
-Oh, is it?
GOVERNMENT SCHOOL
Who placed pride
Inside the dress of a woman?
Oh, does the culture get spoiled
If we cut our hair?
Get lost, you guys
They kept men in the front
And women at the back
They made the women
Who used to drive away tigers
Spin baskets
To keep the chicken safe
The people who try to enslave us
Should run away
Run, run, run, you guys
Are we here with you
To broom the floor?
After going around
He got caught by the right woman
Thinking he was hurting the ant
He hurt the lion's tooth
She is valorous
And can fight one-on-one
She took a wooden block
And swirled
Madam should come
and inaugurate our textile shop.
-Madam, are you planning to join politics?
-No!
Hey, who's that in the frame?
Get out of the frame.
Nonsense!
Go to your left!
We respectfully welcome
our mighty freedom fighter brother Ratnam!
Brother, now you're on the list
of freedom fighters.
Are you serious?
Everyone who serves a sentence
calls themselves one.
Why not you do the same?
It doesn't cost a dime.
Hey, where is my nephew?
Has he forgotten me after the marriage?
He didn't even come to receive me.
I'll explain everything later.
To sum up, Veera is roaming like a corpse.
It's he who is responsible for all of it.
Ratnam.
Ratnam, I heard you got out of prison.
I want to meet you right away.
Where are you?
I'm at Veera's house. Where are you?
Hey, go to Veera's house.
-Please eat.
-Fish curry, is it?
-Bring me fish fry.
-Sure, I'll get it.
Fry it well.
How do you sleep at night?
I trusted you and got my nephew married.
How could you betray me?
You seem very angry.
We should not discuss family matters
when we're angry.
Please sit down and have food.
-Keerthi made a mean fish curry--
-Hey!
Do you think I'm here to attend a feast?
Your folks did not have any sense.
And lied to get you married.
Don't you have any sense?
Ratnam, I'm the one to blame here.
Yell at me all you want.
Not her. She's a poor thing.
Hey, she's fighting like a rogue
on the streets.
-She's not a poor thing.
-Don't talk like a fool.
Had she not made it on time that day,
they would've killed Veera.
It would've been better if he got killed.
It's better to get killed by an enemy
than saved by a woman.
My husband's life is more important
than your family's pride.
No woman would stay silent
when her husband is about to get killed.
Moreover, I'm a wrestler.
I will fight!
You should have raised her like a woman.
If you raise her like a man, she'll fight.
Uncle, ask him to leave.
Hey, you don't have the right
to send me out.
Speak with respect.
Hey, this is how I speak to women.
You're not special!
It would be best if you raised a girl
to be modest and obedient.
If not, they'll talk back like a rogue!
Hey, Keerthi, what have you done?
How long will you keep up
the charade of moral policing women?
Don't we know how to lead our life?
Would you keep lecturing for life?
Hey, why did you slap him?
Male chauvinists like him
should be taught a lesson.
Ratnam!
Hey, Ratnam, please stop.
I said, stop!
She's innocent. It was a mistake.
-Hey, where is she?
-What happened?
She's inside. Hey!
Just because you're strong,
you will beat anyone as you please?
Do you know your uncle disrespected me?
That doesn't give you the right
to slap him.
-Hear me out--
-Keerthi!
He is right.
No matter what,
you should not have slapped him.
Come on, let's go and apologize to Ratnam.
She will apologize to him.
An apology won't make things right.
I never said I'm going to apologize.
Please don't add fuel to the problem.
Apologizing once won't make us any lesser.
Let's go!
First, ask his uncle to apologize
for demeaning women.
After that,
I'll apologize for slapping him.
What did you say?
You expect my uncle to apologize to you?
Such arrogance?
-This is not going to work.
-Veera… Listen…
Why are you being short with your in-laws?
I never said anything wrong.
You know me well.
A girl should never be short
with her in-laws.
Uncle, you do know how he spoke to me.
Hey, you don't belong
in this house anymore. Get out!
-Son, it was a mistake.
-Hey, get lost!
-It's all because of you.
-I agree it's me!
I beg of you not to do this.
-Let go!
-Don't throw her out of the house.
Uncle, you don't have to beg him.
He's not even ready
to hear what his uncle said.
Then how could you expect him
to understand my anger?
Dear, please don't act in haste.
Please hear me out.
Slapping his uncle is not
the only reason he's throwing me out.
I saved his life in front of the village.
He could not bear the humiliation.
An egoistic man will turn a deaf ear
to things that hurt his manhood.
The day when he lets go of his male ego
and understands that I'm right,
I will return to this house.
Get going!
Is my life on fire?
Are you the one who set it on?
Why did I trust you?
Why are you making me suffer?
I will hide from your vision
Is this enough, dear?
Will the feather that has lost its way
Fall in the breeze?
I will suffer even after
The pain vanishes
Words have hurt me so much
I have gifted you, my love
Through separation
So that you are at peace!
Have you forgotten?
Aren't you the tree
Whose heart has dried?
Have you forgotten?
My soul is cracking
Aren't you the tree
Whose heart has dried?
Have you forgotten?
My soul is cracking
You let go of my hand
You'd have to show me the way back
You'll have to find me a pit
To bury my heart deep in sorrow
Uncle, what is this?
What do you mean?
Submission Wrestling Championship.
Who is taking part?
Athira, Akila and Keerthi.
Hey, I don't remember you telling me
you're participating in the championship.
Stop pretending.
Who asked you to enroll me?
-I did not--
-I enrolled you, dear.
Please don't yell at him.
I'm surprised that you enrolled her.
Yes, I enrolled her.
Why, dad?
Only when you play,
do you forget yourself.
Go and play your sport.
I don't want to.
It has already caused too many problems.
If I go ahead and play,
it will fuel the existing problems.
I won't get it resolved.
Have you lost your mind?
Are you going to make it worse
and separate them?
Go and speak to Veera's uncle
and find a way to send her back
to her in-laws.
To hell with the competition!
I did meet Veera's uncle.
When was this?
After all that you did,
how could you even face me?
Is this how you raise your daughter?
She beats up people.
Didn't you teach her any discipline?
I apologize on behalf of everything
that happened.
Please be a bigger person
and bring them back together.
Your daughter won't suit our family.
You may leave. I said, leave!
He did not even invite you
inside the house?
Such arrogance!
-I should have met him--
-Hey, don't yell!
The mistake is on our side.
Give it time.
Everything will fall into place.
Let my daughter be her old self
until things get back to normal.
Hi!
I thought she'd return, pleading
and apologizing to me.
Instead, she went back to wrestling.
Let her do it, son. Let her do it!
If she has moved on.
Let's move on as well.
Don't worry about anything.
Soon I'll find a better match than her
and get you married.
Uncle, you have done enough!
I don't want another marriage.
To hell with marriage!
-Pissing me off!
-Hey, Veera!
Brother, he's damn pissed off!
After all, he's my nephew.
He's yelling out of frustration.
If we leave him be,
he may commit suicide one day.
I won't let it happen!
We will find him a new match immediately.
Before that, we need to send
a divorce notice to the wrestler.
-Do you know how to send a notice?
-How could you doubt me?
According to
Indian Constitution Section 407--
-Do you know or not?
-I know, brother!
-Immediately send it.
-Sure, I will.
Girls! You're doing it wrong.
Can you hold this for me?
Okay!
So, take the leg back. Yeah!
Yeah! That's the position!
Okay? Got it?
-Lokesh!
-Hmm.
-Over here.
Thank you!
We have a lot of
tournament work to finish.
As soon as you stepped in,
you started your antics.
I can't help it. She's so freaking hot!
Mind you! She's married!
Really?
Wow!
I'm more comfortable with married women.
Hey!
They're only fit for such things.
It's not like they're going to
achieve anything
by taking training
and playing for the country.
-Why would you say that?
-I don't believe all these girls.
Brother, come right away to the quarry.
Is there a problem?
Trust me. Get here right away!
-Stop right there.
-Come on, fight!
Come on, fight me!
Pick it up. Pick it up, damn it!
Let's fight it out!
Let's see who is the last man standing.
Do you think I'm here to fight
and kill you?
You died on the day when your wife
fought and saved your life.
In my opinion, you're a dead snake!
I can even go to a fight with an infant.
But I will never fight you!
It's an insult to fight you.
Do you know something?
Since your wife beat me up,
my wife stopped giving me respect.
She spits at me,
stating that a woman had beaten me up.
Hey, who the hell called me?
-Brother, it was me.
-Come here!
I said, come here!
Instead of informing over the phone…
You kept yelling, asking me to come here.
If you again involve me in his matters,
I'll kill you all and go to prison.
I was peacefully watching
soap operas on TV.
Bloody got me all worked up!
Hey!
Fight me!
Get lost!
Did you pass out religiously,
or did you cheat?
-Why does he look worked up?
-I wonder what happened today?
-Hey, add some water--
-Hey, nephew!
What happened?
Years of respect and honor
went down the drain.
Das is calling me a dead snake!
People have forgotten
that my name is Veera.
They call me Keerthi's husband!
Uncle, I don't feel like living.
I want to jump into a well and die.
Didn't I tell you?
Son, I understand your feelings.
I would've hung myself long ago
if I were in your place.
Suicide?
Yesterday, I asked Melathur Manickam's
daughter's hand in marriage for you.
-Do you know what he said?
-What did he say?
Your nephew will create problems
at the bar.
He will create problems
at the council meeting
He'll also create problems at a temple.
My daughter can't go fight everywhere
and save him.
I did not raise her to fight.
-What does it mean?
-What does it mean, uncle?
It means you can't walk alone on the
street without your wife accompanying you.
Oh God, no!
I don't want to stay alive
bearing such humiliation.
I'm going to die right away.
-Hey, this drink won't kill you.
-Let go of it.
There's a white color bottle
inside the motor room.
Go and have that drink.
-I'm going to die.
-Hey!
Death won't bring back your honor.
You'll be labeled that you died of shame.
We should find your honor
where you lost it.
Instead, if you look elsewhere,
you won't gain anything,
nor you'll earn back your honor.
What are you getting at?
Your wife proved to people
that she's stronger than you.
Now you should prove to the same people
that you're stronger than your wife.
You want me to fight again
with Das's men at the carnival?
-That's not what I am saying.
-Then?
Next month your wife is taking part
in a wrestling championship.
Yes!
You, too, take part in
the same competition
and fight her one and one!
He's doomed!
What is there to think?
After that, the people
of this village will respect you more.
Brother, have you lost it?
How can he take part
in the women's championship?
According to Section 407,
there's no such rule.
-Yes.
-To hell with your rules.
It's common abroad.
Didn't we watch this on TV?
We will request them to implement it.
It's high time India develops.
-He does not know wrestling.
-Yeah!
It's not rocket science!
It's kabaddi in our state
and wrestling in theirs.
Are you saying that kabaddi
and wrestling are the same?
All competitions are the same!
Only the name differs!
I'm saying you take part
in the competition.
You'll emerge a winner. Jai Hind!
Hey, try to understand.
It's a women's competition.
Only ladies can take part
in this competition.
You can enroll yourself
in men's wrestling.
That's not going to happen.
My nephew will take part
in the women's competition.
It's about his honor!
Listen, this is not regular wrestling.
It's submission kusthi!
I don't care about your aspiration!
Kusthi means modern freestyle wrestling.
It's played on a mat.
But submission kusthi
is old traditional wrestling.
It is played on sand.
-It's tough!
-You don't bother about it.
Right from birth,
we've been playing in the sand.
Gilli, Beads, Top, titillating games,
stick fight, we've played many games
that you did not.
We are mighty sportspersons!
End your nonsense and enroll my nephew.
Put down my name!
Hello! Yes, sir.
They're a great nuisance.
I'm coming to you.
He's a nuisance himself
and calling us one.
I'll handle you once you return.
What is the problem?
Sir, they have come from Pollachi.
They are determined to fight
against Keerthi.
Her husband is adamant about
taking part in this competition.
They're having problems at home.
And they're trying to sort it out
through this competition.
This is not the place
to settle family matters.
Ask them to go to court. Idiots!
If they go to court,
it'll take years to resolve it.
They're here to settle it right away.
There's nothing wrong with it.
That does not mean we can arrange
a match for them.
-Forget it!
-Why can't we do it?
There has never been a match conducted
between a husband and a wife.
What if?
Sir, the schedule
for the competition is locked.
Announce it as a special category match.
It's all up to us!
Why are you so eager
to organize this match?
Come on!
This match will benefit you and your club.
How?
If a husband and a wife clash in a match,
the public will be excited to watch it.
Sponsors will come to us.
We will get a lot of advertisements.
We can hike ticket prices
and make a lot of money.
I spoke to the Managing Director.
He appreciated your eagerness
and agreed to organize the match.
Hey, that's awesome, nephew!
Is it he, who is taking part
in the competition?
Precisely!
-Name?
-Veera!
Veera.
Are you a wrestling champion
from Tamil Nadu?
I'm going to train for it.
-Let's go.
-Come on, let's get you trained.
Brother, they're doing it on purpose.
What do they know about wrestling?
I've been wrestling for twenty years,
yet I'm not familiar.
What happened?
Ratnam is the root cause of it.
At least for that reason,
Keerthi should take part in the
competition and slam our son-in-law.
Have you people lost your minds?
How do you expect them
to get back together
if she wrestles with her husband?
Keerthi, go and remove yourself
from the competition.
Let's get rid of this wrestling for good!
Sir, post!
What is it?
They're pushing it far!
They have sent her a divorce notice!
How could we still stay patient with them?
They've crossed all limits!
They have decided to end ties.
We have to revert with a fitting response.
God, please help us!
Dear God!
I am going to take part
in this competition.
Keerthi.
Kodangi Wrestling Society.
This place looks weird.
Why did you bring me here?
He's the best wrestling coach
in this area.
I can win against Keerthi,
only if I train with him.
Oh!
He is the coach.
He looks a bit weird to me.
They're screaming like fools.
And you've come here to train.
Why are they jogging on the spot?
Hey!
-Let's go.
-Go!
-Greetings, coach!
-Who are you people?
-I'm Veera, and he's Sattam.
-I did not ask for your names.
Stupids! What brings you here?
I want to train for fifteen days
in submission wrestling
and become a Champion.
Please bless me, coach!
It's not a sambhar recipe
that you can learn in fifteen days.
-It's wrestling, damn it!
-I know, coach.
I have enrolled in a reputed competition.
If I don't win, I'll lose face!
-You already lost your face.
-Shut up!
Do you know submission wrestling?
I know kabaddi, coach.
Kabaddi, kabaddi, kabaddi!
-Hey, what is this nonsense?
-Kabaddi, kabaddi…
When I asked if you knew wrestling,
you should say yes or no.
Instead, you're playing kabaddi.
Are you a fool?
He's not a fool. But his uncle is a fool.
It was he who told him
that kabaddi and wrestling are the same.
Go and train with that fool.
Coach, please hear me out.
Coach, coach. Please, coach.
My life is in your hands.
Why are you so eager
about this competition?
I'll explain, coach.
-My wife, she's--
-Hmm!
I understood!
I'll tell you the rest.
Your wife is sick,
and you need money for the treatment.
So, you're taking part in the competition
to win the prize money.
Am I correct?
-I…
-I told you, he's weird.
How did you find out, coach?
I can relate to you.
As my wife was sick,
I took part in a wrestling competition
and won the prize money.
I am very proud of you!
I will train you in wrestling.
-Thank you, coach.
-You can join us from tomorrow.
If he comes to know you are competing
against your wife,
he will beat you to death.
Don't blurt it out!
Hey, what are you doing over here?
I joined long ago.
You're late to the party.
My wife found out I was part of
the Husband Protection Committee.
She entered the office and beat me up!
That's why I came here.
Mic Mohan tried to turn into
Mic Tyson overnight
If you go near him to fight
He will try to stab
And bite your ears
Hold it tight!
Bring it on!
When you hold,
you got to lock your right hand
and left hand this way and twist it.
Mic Mohan tried to turn into…
Coach, coach! It's hurting.
If you wish to become a champion
in 15 days, you have to work hard.
Hey, you're next!
I don't mind waiting for fifteen years.
I'm not in a hurry.
You go!
Who do you think I am
The master is on our side
Hold tight and pin him down!
-Gear up!
-Block!
Everybody feeling go around
With the power
Hold on, everybody take cover
When we give it you
Gatta Kusthi!
Hey, wake up!
Everybody feeling…
Ladies are up and training.
And you here are sleeping like a log!
I'm not able to get up.
I have a body ache.
Come on!
I have brought myself trouble
Thinking I was getting a companion
Raise your head.
I will drive away the evil spirit
For the mistake I committed
Of marrying her, I need to fight
I am really getting angry
With you! With you!
Hey!
This is easy because it's a doll.
But your wife is real.
She'll hit you back!
But you'll be the first husband
in the world to train hard
to beat up his wife.
Mic Mohan tried to turn into…
-Don't give up. Keep running!
-Mic Tyson overnight
If you go near him to fight
He will try to stab you
And bite your ears
Who do you think I am
The master is on our side
Coach, you've been training me
every day on this same move.
Is that all you know?
Hey, you only have fifteen days to train.
At least learn one
of the techniques diligently.
Idiot!
I'm quitting!
I will tackle you from the other side.
-Come on, tighten your hands.
-Is this lock, okay?
Oh, no, come on. Come on!
Here, you got to hold it tight.
Here, go on!
Your talent deserves more.
Come with me to the Punjab Academy.
If you train over there,
you can win against any player in India.
Coach, why are you asking me
to squeeze this fruit?
This is a technique too.
Your grasp should
squeeze the pulp out of it.
Squeeze it. Squeeze it strong.
Squeeze it until the fruit pops out.
What? Step aside.
A slash will do the job.
Instead, you're listening to the fool
and squeezing it.
Who do you think I am
The master is on our side
Hold him like this.
You are caught hold of by a woman
It's high time to buck up
Hey, he's training us for everything
but wrestling.
We could do this back home ourselves.
He is making us do--
Oh, God, no!
Bring it on!
If I come
I will drive you away
Please don't compete in this competition.
Please listen to me.
To hell with you!
You have never listened to me.
Too much arrogance is not suitable
for a woman.
-Aren't you going for training?
-No!
I'm afraid I'll lose the match.
Don't worry. You will win.
What makes you say it?
-Did you watch Sarpatta?
-Yes, I did.
Anyone who trained with coach Ranga
did not win.
In the end, Kabilan, a spectator,
won the match.
In Irudhi Suttru,
the elder sister trained since childhood.
But the younger sister
that watched TV won the match.
Whereas in Badri,
boxing was life for the elder brother.
But in the end,
Thalapathy Vijay won the trophy.
What do you make of it?
To win a match, It's enough
that you're a spectator in a game.
You're perfect for being a spectator!
Oh, no!
KODANGI WRESTLING SOCIETY
-What would people say?
-Dad, don't do this.
-What would I say to our relatives?
-Dad, I want to play.
-Let go of me. Please, dad!
-Why don't you listen?
Get inside the car. Stop being stubborn.
-Get inside.
-Dad, please!
Dad, please, I don't want to get married.
Dad, please!
-What are you doing?
-It's been two months
since my daughter left home.
We don't know what happened to her.
Or where did she go?
Her mother is worried and fell sick.
Aren't you a coach?
At least you could've informed us.
Here you go! This is for taking care
of my daughter.
-Start the car!
-Dad, please, this is my dream.
It's her dream
to achieve big in wrestling.
But her folks have found a match for her.
She did not agree to it
and ran away from home.
Boys and girls!
Do you know why I threw a party?
Just with the training of fifteen days,
a person is ready to compete
in a huge competition.
That is no one but our Veera!
This party is to wish him success.
When you win the match,
who would you dedicate the victory to?
-I'll dedicate it to you, coach!
-No, no!
You have to dedicate it to your wife.
Hey, only winners can dedicate.
I wonder why are you guys
arguing about it.
Yes, coach!
-Hey, where are you going?
-I'm hungry. I'm going to eat.
Coach, I often hear you talk
about your wife.
It's been years since she passed.
Do you still miss her?
As days go by, I miss her more.
I was an alcoholic.
It was she who turned me
into an honest man.
She took me to her father
and made me train in wrestling.
And one day we got married.
It was her all along.
We can even remain a beggar.
But we should not remain alone
without a wife during our last days.
Didn't you ever fight with your wife?
There's no room for fights when there are
no expectations in a relationship.
When there are expectations involved,
that'll attract fights.
And that, my boy,
we call husband and wife fights.
There was not one day we did not fight.
We fought like mad.
The moment you marry your wife,
She becomes the undisputed queen
of the family.
She makes the decisions!
Only executing them is a husband's job.
If you understand this fact,
there will be no problems in marriage.
I don't get it, coach!
A few families still fight
despite dancing to their wife's tunes.
In every marriage,
until they get to know each other
for the first ten-fifteen years,
they will tend to fight.
Does it get resolved after fifteen years?
It won't resolve right away.
Similar to the continuous drizzle
after heavy rain.
Seven to eight years later,
there will be small unresolved disputes.
Would it get any better after that?
After that,
both will be fifty-sixty years old.
Both won't have the strength to fight.
That period of our life
will be the most peaceful.
How does it matter if you lead a life
after you're sixty?
He pegs himself to be Shakespeare.
Churning out philosophy.
And you're listening to him.
Auntie, is uncle home?
He went out.
He'll be back soon. Sit down.
Is the competition tomorrow, Veera?
Yes, auntie. It's tomorrow.
How was the training?
Don't even ask.
They squeezed the life out of me.
The coach never lets me rest.
Heavy workout! I'm still not able
to move my hands and legs.
No matter how much you train,
you can't win against her.
Why are you toiling yourself?
You could've appeared straight
to the match.
Auntie, you've decided that I will lose.
The moment you decided
to compete with your wife,
you lost the match!
Your uncle is a fool.
But you're a bigger fool than him.
Would anyone in this world be ready
to compete with his wife?
Men like you want your women
to abide by you.
Am I right?
Tell me something.
Would you be able to live without women?
You need a woman your entire life.
Mother, until you get married.
After marriage, it's your wife.
You may ask,
could women live without men?
Many women have raised
their children being single.
But men tend to remarry immediately.
Their excuse would be
for the sake of children.
It's his children too.
Why can't he take care of them?
He won't!
Because he does not know how to.
Do you know what the purpose
of marriage is?
Men are opportunists!
They are self-centered.
To change that trait,
God gets them married to a woman.
A woman enters a man's life,
and children are born.
Now he lives for them.
It may be a burden for him.
But even if he can't bear it,
there's meaning to his life.
Listen, I knew that your wife was a
wrestler right from the beginning.
Auntie,
why didn't you tell me this sooner?
Had I told you, this marriage
wouldn't have happened.
I thought if a girl like Keerthi
is in your life,
she would change you and your way of life.
That is why I did not say.
Veera, one day,
when you were not home,
I took Keerthi to the temple.
Have you forgotten wrestling?
They say anything you do for 48 days
becomes a habit.
For fifteen years,
I only thought about wrestling.
I cannot forget it.
Then what made you choose this life?
We all are slaves of our family.
When the choice is between
family and career,
we can only choose family.
It's true!
But people who are determined
to make it big
should not consider family.
You should turn a deaf ear
and continue to pursue your dream.
It's easier said than done.
Players from other countries
have to compete only with their opponents.
But in India,
first, you need to compete
with the family and win.
You'll be half tired.
After that, we won't have the energy
to compete with the opponents.
Do you like this life?
I like him very much.
Look, Veera,
you're lucky to have Keerthi
as your wife.
Please try to make it work.
Instead, if you listen to your uncle,
you'll be out on the streets in despair.
I can't believe you speak so much.
Do you know how far I have studied?
Fourth grade, right?
I graduated with a BA
in English Literature.
Even my father lied
and got me married to your uncle.
The match is tomorrow.
We'll see who wins. Kerala or Tamil Nadu?
I'll hang up.
Son, when did you arrive?
Just now.
Did she ask you for a cup of coffee?
I'm good. I'm leaving.
What? What were you doing?
I was talking to him.
As if you're a big shot
discussing current affairs.
Go! Go and get us coffee!
Listen! Two coffees. Full strong!
One, me. One, nephew!
Nephew coffee, full sugar.
My coffee, no sugar.
Understood? Go and make coffee.
I hope you understand
and won't add too much sugar.
I am already diabetic!
What is it?
-Do you like this life?
-I like him very much.
You're lucky to have Keerthi as your wife.
Please try to make it work.
-With this, the over is done.
-Hey, catch the ball.
Uncle, we'll take the ball.
Hey, I can't get in. Move the cupboard.
-Pull it hard.
-Here, move to the side.
Damn, it's so heavy!
Oh, no!
Hey, why are you making so much noise?
Hey, come on, let's run!
Sorry, uncle, we dropped it.
Keerthi! Keerthi! Keerthi!
Action!
Hold on! Who are you?
What do you want?
-My wife is here.
-It's a women's training center.
-I want to meet my wife.
-Men are not allowed.
Please tell the manager I'm here.
You can check with him.
-Any problem?
-My wife Keerthi is inside.
I want to meet her.
He is not allowing me.
Oh, so you're Keerthi's husband.
Yes, sir.
-Stay right here. I'll inform Keerthi.
-Okay, sir.
What did she say? May I come in?
Keerthi is not interested in meeting you.
She said, "If you're man enough,
fight it out in the arena."
You may leave!
Keerthi, come on, get up.
Let's start the practice.
Practice? That too now?
No chance! I cannot!
I'm so tired!
At least we can go jogging.
Oh, no!
For God's sake, spare me.
I'm going home.
Okay!
Coach!
Who was it?
Submission wrestling is organized
by Palakkad Wrestling Association.
Everyone is invited to watch.
In the upcoming submission wrestling,
a man and his wife are about
to fight each other.
What's your opinion
on the Veera-Keerthi wrestling match?
It's an evil world. I have nothing to say.
-Your opinion?
-Life is wrestling itself.
Veera is the only man who is fighting
for men's liberation.
We have taken an oath
to go on a pilgrimage and shave our heads.
-What do you say, guys?
-Yes!
It does not matter whether it is a man
or a woman. The best one should win.
Women who fight for equal rights, ask them
to take part in the competition.
How long do wives abide by their husbands?
Bring it on!
The women have started to strike back.
It's high time patriarchy ends.
You may speak all you want.
But men are above anything.
Then let's witness the rest
at the stadium.
-It's very interesting news.
-Okay.
We are waiting. Let's enjoy!
People eagerly wait to see who wins
the match between man and wife.
The girl will win!
The girl will win for sure.
Veera will win!
Keerthi!
We are Keerthi Army!
Submission wrestling
is a 100-year-old tradition in Kerala.
This competition is
in the honor of Kerala.
It's the game of the people!
The competition we all have been
waiting for
Is about to begin in a while.
Come on clap!
On behalf of our academy,
we invite you all.
More than fifty wrestlers are about to
take part in 36 competitions.
Ultimately, a wife and a husband
will compete under a special category.
The first round is about to begin.
Wrestler Unni has thrown a stronghold
in the beginning.
The opponent bites the dust.
Kannur Veerangai from Trivandrum
is trying to slam Lakshmi.
She won the match!
Wow! An Unbelievable
and unexpected attack from Sreejith.
Is it Marimuthu?
Yeah, we're at the council office.
My nephew's match is about to begin.
Hurry up!
What a performance, Veena!
Veena's efforts didn't go to waste.
She's celebrating her victory.
Wow, Gopi just slammed Sarath
to the ground.
Palakkad Keda Kumar unexpectedly
lost to Ernakulam Suresh!
One of the important matches
of this tournament is on.
Wow, what a throw! Amazing throw!
Sir!
As a wrestling coach,
who do you think will win?
Veera or Keerthi?
No doubt about it.
Keerthi will be the winner.
Veera is going to get beaten to death.
The media is just hyping him up.
He is not worth it.
Keerthi.
Are you okay?
Are you wondering how
to compete with your husband?
It was not your decision.
He voluntarily asked
to arrange this match.
You have
to knock him down in the first round.
Don't worry. I'm there for you.
Take your hands off.
I said, take your hands off!
What?
Hey, come on, Keerthi!
Players have complained about you.
For the way you treat women.
Get lost!
I just received the report.
What could I do?
Any problem?
Keerthi is pregnant.
During the fitness check before the match,
Mrs. Keerthi tested positive
for pregnancy.
-Is Keerthi aware of it?
-No!
What are you going to do?
What else?
We have to cancel the match.
Let's not cancel the match.
As per the plan,
let us proceed with the match.
How? What if something goes wrong?
There is no other option.
The show must go on!
Let's not do it, sir.
Due to strain during the match,
there are chances of abortion.
If this match is canceled,
we'll lose millions.
Who will answer the audience?
Who will answer the sponsors?
Would you answer them?
Sir, you're talking about business.
But I'm talking about life.
The husband and wife are going to fight
and go their separate ways.
It does not matter if something
goes wrong with the child.
I will take responsibility for everything.
As long as you stay silent, we're good.
-I can't stay silent--
-Hey, don't you understand?
Stop with your nonsense.
Let's go!
The most anticipated fight of all,
the Veera-Keerthi wrestling match
is about to begin.
Even in the Olympics, we don't get
to witness a match of this kind.
Husband vs. wife in the same arena!
The wrestling
that was happening within four walls
has moved to the arena now!
Come on, fight!
Come on, ready!
Contact! Contact!
Come on, Veera!
Hold tight! Don't let go!
Hey!
Step away! Step away!
Keerthi!
-Hey, step away!
-Keerthi!
-I said, step away.
-Keerthi, what happened?
-Keerthi!
I told you!
Come on, hurry up. Take her away.
She fainted.
What will happen now?
Hurry up!
Take her inside the ambulance.
-Come on, hurry up!
-Be careful!
-Where are you going?
-Hey, get down from the ambulance.
-Why are you getting inside?
-She's my wife!
-Hey, pull him down.
-Hey, she's my wife!
-I need to go to the hospital.
-Please hear me out!
What the hell is wrong with you people?
Sattam, please tell them.
Have you guys lost your mind?
I need to go to the hospital.
Let go of me! I said, let go of me!
Doctors will take care of her.
You go and play the match.
Are you kidding?
I came here only
to compete with my wife.
I don't know what happened to her.
And you want me to play the match.
It'll become a big issue
if the match does not go on.
As per committee rules,
you will have to face another wrestler.
I can't compete with this girl.
We are not asking you to fight a man.
We are asking you to fight a woman.
Are you afraid to lose to a girl?
Humiliation is not a new thing to you.
So, go on!
It wasn't bright of me to compete
against my wife.
That does not mean
I'll fight any woman in the town.
If I must play a match,
I'll fight you.
If you're a man, fight me!
Hey, Veera, have you lost your mind?
He's a champion coach.
And you want to fight him?
I don't care.
He's talking too much, Sattam.
He'll pipe down
if I punch him in the face.
Do you know who he is?
During a match in Delhi,
his punch killed his opponent.
And you're challenging him to a match.
Sir, I care less about his performance.
I don't know what happened to my wife.
He's not letting me go to the hospital.
He's gone mad lamenting about rules.
I'm ready to fight, only if it's him.
If not, I will leave right away.
I can't help it
if you have a death wish.
Come on!
Veera!
Here he comes!
Action!
Up! Up! Up! Come on!
Come on!
Come on! Come on!
Hey!
Hit him back!
That's it! Come on, Veera!
Hey, what the hell are you doing?
Come on, get up!
-Oh!
-Hey!
You can't play foul. Step out!
Hey, what the hell?
-Sir, sir, sir!
-Hey!
Hey!
He stepped out of the ring.
Foul! Foul!
Shall I tell you a secret?
Usually, a wife conveys this secret
to the husband.
Unfortunately, your wife itself
does not know the secret.
Let me tell you the secret.
You're going to be a father.
Hey! Hey!
Keerthi is pregnant.
That is why she fainted.
I didn't care for her pregnancy
and made her compete.
But your child is blessed with long life.
It escaped.
If not, you would have killed your child--
-Go, Veera!
-Slam that man!
Come on! Slam him!
Veera! Veera!
Veera!
Here he comes!
Veera, you nailed it.
Bring it on!
That's it. That's it.
Pin him down!
Don't let go. Pin him down!
Awesome!
Doctor, he's fighting dirty.
Forget it, sir.
The audience is enjoying the fight.
That's what we want.
Super!
Awesome! Wow!
Let go of him!
Let go!
Let go of him, Veera!
Let go of me!
-Let go.
-I won't!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Lokesh is down.
What a performance by Veera.
Unbelievable attack!
What a man! He's stubborn!
-Unexpectedly, Veera emerged as a winner.
-That's my boy!
Veera, you're a champion!
To whom do you dedicate this victory?
I dedicate this victory
to my wife, Keerthi.
You came here to compete
with your wife.
What is the reason you're dedicating it
to your wife?
I did not come to compete
or win against Keerthi.
I came to know a few things
about Keerthi.
I came down to convince her
and take her back home.
I wanted to convey that women
are nothing less than a man.
That's why I did not care
if I won or lost.
I wanted to prove to the world
through this match,
that in life, some of us will take time
to understand a few things.
I understood just now.
Until yesterday, I believed
men were above women.
Keerthi proved me wrong.
I thought wrestling was easy
as it is played on the sand.
And went to train.
Had I not taken the training,
I would've not known the struggle
Keerthi went through.
I trained only for fifteen days.
I could not take it.
My whole body was in pain.
But a girl has been doing it
for fifteen years.
I can't imagine the pain she went through.
Sports and India are far apart.
Here, even the boys get told to study
rather than play sports, let alone girls.
Girls who overcome obstacles
to play sports are forced to get married
and suppress their dreams and goals.
They get lectured on life and family.
If given proper training
and family support,
a million girls in India will win
the Olympic gold medal.
One gold among the million is Keerthi.
All this while,
I did not recognize her worth.
So, I apologize to my gold
in front of you people.
Please forgive me, Keerthi.
Your husband won over you
without competing with you.
Keerthi…
Hello, what are you doing?
Can't you see?
I'm putting her on a drip.
My wife doesn't need it!
Do you know who she is?
A wrestler!
Keerthi, if we don't leave,
they'll pile on the bill with the drip.
Come on, let's go.
You sent a divorce notice.
How could you even face her?
She won't go with you.
Please leave.
Dear, why would you
tell the nurse about our affairs?
You need not put her on a drip.
Please leave.
-Go on. Leave.
-Sir!
My stupid uncle and the lawyer sent
the divorce notice without my knowledge.
Tear it up and throw it away!
Let's go.
I had a dream
to make it big in this sport.
I couldn't make it.
But I wish for my child
to play for this country.
That won't happen if I stay
with you. So, please leave.
Why do you think you couldn't make it?
It's not like you're old.
Marikann played even after having a child.
She also won a medal for the country.
In fact, she had three children.
Marikann?
The boxer.
They even made a film about her.
Do you mean Mary Kom?
Be it Mary or Mari,
all I'm saying is you can do it too.
I will help you win.
-Are you sure?
-I swear I will.
It's enough if you
compete with the opponents.
You need not compete
with the family anymore.
You won't go back on your word, right?
I swear on our child I won't.
Keerthi! Keerthi! Keerthi!
Hey, clap for your mom!